Privacy Policy
==============

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for DAREBEE (darebee.com). This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site.

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We do not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We do not and will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to delete your forum (The Hive) account.

We do not engage in any email marketing and will not bother you with any communication from us. 

You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

* See what data we have about you, if any.
* Change/correct any data we have about you.
* Have us delete any data we have about you.
* Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Security:** We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit  information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. We do not collect any sensitive data like credit cards or your home address.

**Apps:** None of the DAREBEE apps (FitTap and others) collect any information about you. 

**Google Analytics:** DAREBEE resource uses Google Analytics.

**Updates:** Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

**Cookies:** This website uses cookies to track your fitness progress (for saving Challenge and Pandora fitness quest progress). You can disable cookies any time but keep in mind that then the "save" button on some pages will not work.

* * *

Funding Level

26%

* * *

### Get Started

New to DAREBEE? Start here:

### the Project

DAREBEE is a non-profit, ad-free and product placement free global fitness resource. DAREBEE is supported exclusively via [user donations](https://www.darebee.com/support.html).  
  
[**DAREBEETS**](https://darebeets.com/) - just like DAREBEE, but with food.  
  
© 2012 - 2024 DAREBEE | All Rights Reserved. This website uses Cookies. [Disclaimer](https://www.darebee.com/disclaimer.html) & [Privacy Policy](https://www.darebee.com/privacy). All of the materials on this website are unique, copyrighted and are exclusive to darebee.com.

In other languages: [French](https://darebee.fr/) | [Greek](https://darebee.gr/) | [Russian](https://darebee.net/)
